Amy: 12:30 – In a long line outside the Conference Center.
Security guard: Can I see your ID, please?
Amy: Here’s my passport.
Security guard: Thanks. “Amy Jones.”
And I need to check your bag, please.
OK, come in.
Next, please!
Amy: 12:45 – In the waiting area with 350 other singers!
Organizer 1: OK, Amy, sit here and wait until we call your name.
Amy: Thanks.
Organizer 1: Are you here for the audition, too?
Friend: No, I’m not. I’m Amy’s friend.
Can I wait with her?
Organizer 1: Yeah, sure.
Friend: Thanks.
Amy: Let’s sit here. I’m so nervous…
Organizer 1: Matteo Ricci, Jada Jackson, Tony Cash, come with me, please.
This way.
Amy: Good luck!
4 o’clock – Three hours later! My turn at last!
Organizer 2: Amy Jones, Naomi Williams, Dan Elliot?
Can you come with me, please? It’s your turn now.
Amy: Oh my goodness! It’s my turn.
Friend: Good luck, Amy! You can do it!
Amy: Excuse me. Can my friend come with me?
Organizer 2: No, she can’t. She can wait there.
And you can’t take your bag into the audition. Leave it with your friend.
Amy: OK.
4:15 – In the audition, with two judges. Really nervous!
Judge: Amy…Jones?
What’s your song?
Amy: One Day.
Judge: We can’t hear you. Is the microphone on?
Amy: Sorry. Sorry.
Can you hear me now?
Judge: Yes, that’s fine.
Amy: My song’s One Day.
Judge: Can you start, please?
Amy: Oh no! I can’t remember the first line.
Judge: Take your time.
Amy: I’m OK now!